const quizData = [
    {
        question: "Which language runs in a web browser",
        a: "C",
        b: "C++",
        c: "JavaScript",
        d: "Python",
        correct:"c",
    },
    {
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        a: "HypeText Mark Language",
        b: "HypeText Markup Language",
        c: "HighText Markup Language",
        d: "None of the above",
        correct:"b",
    },
    {
        question: "What does CSS stand for?",
        a: "Cascading Style Sheets",
        b: "Central Style Sheets",
        c: "Cascading Simple Sheets",
        d: "None of the above",
        correct:"a",
    },
    {
        question: "What are the three major languages for web design?",
        a: "Java,HTML,CSS",
        b: "JavaScript,C,HTML",
        c: "JavaScript,HTML,CSS",
        d: "None of the above",
        correct:"c",
    },
    {
        question: "The statement a===b refers to ?",
        a: "Both a and b are equal in value, type and reference address",
        b: "Both a and b are equal in value",
        c: "Both a and b are equal in value and type",
        d: "There is no such statement",
       
        correct: "c",
      },
     {
        question: "Why event handlers is needed in JS?",
        a:"Allows JavaScript code to alter the behaviour of windows",
        b:  "Adds innerHTML page to the code",
        c: "Change the server location",
        d:  "Performs handling of exceptions and occurrences",
        correct: "a",
     },
      {
        question: "The pop() method of the array does which of the following task?",
        a:"decrements the total length by 1" ,
        b: "increments the total length by 1",
        c:"prints the first element but no effect on the length",
        d: " updates the element",
        correct: "a",
     },
     {
        question: "The primary purpose of the array map() function is that it?",
        a: "maps the elements of another array into itself",
        b: "passes each element of the array and returns the necessary mapped elements",
        c: "passes each element of the array on which it is invoked to the function you specify, and returns an array containing the values returnedby that function ",
        d: "pass the elements of the array into another array",
        correct: "c",

      },
      {
        question: "The 'var' and 'function' are?",
        a: "Keywords",
        b: "Declaration statements",
        c: "Data types",
        d: "Prototypes",
        correct: "b",
        
       },
       {
        question: "JavaScript can be written_____?",
        a:"directly into JS file and included into HTML",
        b:"directly on the server page",
        c:"directly into HTML pages",
        d:"directly into the css file",
        correct: "a",
       },
       {
        question: "What is the fundamental rule of lexical scoping?",
        a:"Functions are declared in the scope",
        b:"Functions are executed using scope chain",
        c:"Functions are declared outside the scope",
        d:"Variables are declared within the function",
        correct: "b",
       }
    
];